Privacy Policy
==============

**Grupo Jumex**, as Responsible for the administration of personal data of its End Clients, makes this Integral Privacy Notice available, which follows the Federal Law on Protection of Personal Data Possessed from Individuals and its secondary regulation.

IDENTITY OF RESPONSIBLE ENTITY
------------------------------

* **CORPORATE BUSINESS:** Comercializadora Eloro S.A.
* **CORPORATE NAME:** Grupo Jumex
* **LINE OF BUSINESS:** Production and distribution of juices and nectars
* **WEBSITE:** www.grupojumex.mx
* **TELEPHONE:** (55) 5699-1999
* **ADDRESS:** Carretera México-Pachuca KM 12.5, Colonia Rústica Xalostoc, Ecatepec de Morelos, State of Mexico, Postal Code 55340
* **EMAIL:** privacidad@jumex.com.mx
* **BUSINESS HOURS:** Monday to Thursday from 10:00a.m. to 4:00 pm

TARGET AUDIENCE OF THIS PRIVACY NOTICE
--------------------------------------

This Privacy Notice in its integral Version is addressed to our End Clients.

### Personal Data

LIST OF PERSONAL DATA SUBJECT TO PROCESSING
-------------------------------------------

Grupo Jumex processes several categories of personal data. For your better understanding, the information below details which categories and specific personal data are under our management:

* **Identification Data**
    * CURP (Unique Population Registry Code)
    * Residential Address
    * Age
    * Photograph
    * Official Identification
    * Full Name
    * RFC (Federal Taxpayer Registry)
* **Contact Information**
    * Home and Cellular Phone
    * Personal E-mail address
* **Biometric Data**
    * Voice
    * Signature Verification

SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA
-----------------------

We do not collect or process sensitive personal data of our End Clients.  
In case a change is required, we will inform you of such modification in our Integral Privacy Notice.

HOW DO WE OBTAIN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
-------------------------------------------

* **Directly:**
    * via telephone through our official customer service line: 80001-JUMEX
    * via Email
    * through our official social networks
    * through our Contact form located on our official website: [www.grupojumex.mx](http://www.grupojumex.mx/)
    * through instant messaging (WhatsApp)

PURPOSES OF PROCESSING PERSONAL DATA
------------------------------------

The purpose for managing your personal data is primarily for your understanding and secondly to comply with the provision of law.

PRIMARY PURPOSES
----------------

The primary purpose is that which is necessary for the establishment of a legal obligation or the main reason for which there is a relationship between the Owner (you) and the Data Controller (us), if you object to any of these purposes, Grupo Jumex will be prevented from providing the specific services related to the purpose to which you object.

* **Customer Services**
    * Respond to complaints, comments, or suggestions
    * Provide information about our products and current promotions.
    * Follow up on complaints, comments, and suggestions reports
    * Provide a report number to your complaint
* **Database**
    * Temporarily store incoming calls received through our customer service phone number.
    * Create and manage a database of reports from end customers who contact us through our various communication channels.
* **Customer Service Registry**
    * Temporarily store incoming calls received through our customer service phone number
    * Create and manage a database of reports from end customers who contact us through our various communication channels.
* **Product Sales**
    * Send, to the designated address, the replacement of damaged product and/or tasting packages.
    * Manage shipment, through parcel service, of damaged product to be examined.
    * Manage notifications and cases before PROFECO (Procuraduría Federal del Consumidor).
    * Manage and apply warranties
    * Conduct an operational assessment of the product that has caused health problems.
* **Security**
    * Provide access to and exit from our facilities
    * Provide security through our closed-circuit video surveillance system (we invite you to consult the Privacy Notice displayed in the video surveillance areas).

SECONDARY PURPOSES
------------------

The secondary purpose is not necessary for the establishment of a legal relationship between the Owner (you) and Grupo Jumex Data Controller (us), so you can inform us that you do not authorize the processing of your personal data in any or all the following:

* **Marketing**
    * Send advertising
    * Conduct consumption statistics
* Surveys
    * Conduct satisfaction surveys

Procedure for not accepting secondary purposes
----------------------------------------------

At any time, you can exercise your Rights established in the section “Rights of Access, Rectification, Cancellation and Opposition (ARCO)”.

DISCLOSURE OR PERSONAL DATA
---------------------------

We do not conduct national or international disclosure of your personal data to third parties.

RIGHTS OF ACCESS, RECTIFICATION, CANCELLATION AND OPPOSITION (ARCO)
-------------------------------------------------------------------

WHAT ARE ARCO RIGHTS?
---------------------

ARCO Rights are the legal mechanism that enables you to exercise your Rights of Access, Rectification, Cancellation and Opposition, which consists of:

* Access to personal data that is exclusively yours unless you are a legal representative or guardian of another owner and that are under our management.
* Request that we make corrections or updates to your personal data.
* Request that we delete your personal data when this is legally appropriate.
* Oppose the execution of the primary purposes set forth in this Privacy Notice – in which case, we will be prevented from providing the specific services related to the purpose to which you object.
* Request your opposition to the execution of the secondary purposes indicated.
* Request that your personal data not be transferred to third parties.

MEANS TO EXERCISE YOUR ARCO RIGHTS
----------------------------------

For you to exercise any of your ARCO rights, you must do so personally by following the procedure indicated in the “Procedure to exercise ARCO Rights” section of this Notice.

PROCESS FOR EXERCISING ARCO RIGHTS
----------------------------------

For you to exercise any of your ARCO rights, you must do it personally in accordance with the following detailed section.

The owner of the personal data must request at Carretera México-Pachuca KM 12.5, Colonia Rústica Xalostoc, Ecatepec de Morelos, Estado de México, Postal Code 55340 or at Grupo Jumex’s representative offices in the Mexican Republic, the ARCO Rights request form during business hours from Monday to Thursday from 10:00 to 16:00 hrs., or request it via email to privacidad@jumex.com.mx. The request form must be filled out typewritten or handwritten print. Additionally, the following information will be requested:

* Valid official identification must be submitted in original and copy for verification. If your request is sent electronically, you must attach your scanned identification showing your photo, full name, ID number and signature.
* In case you are not the owner of the personal data, you must attach the document that proves you as a legal representative (Power of Attorney before a Notary Public or Birth Certificate in case of minors represented by a father, mother, or guardian).
* In case of requesting changes derived from corrections or updates, the legal document that accredits this fact must be presented.
* Autographed signature, which must coincide with the official identification presented to carry out the procedure.

Within 5 business days of receiving your request, if there is a question or if we need more information about your request, we will contact you to let you know and obtain more information about the request. You must respond to our request within 10 business days.

Within a period not to exceed 20 business days after receiving your request, or after having answered the clarifications  
requested, we will respond the answer to your request, this answer will be delivered personally at our address or at the Grupo Jumex representative office where you have delivered your request, prior accreditation of the owner or his representative, or in the email address indicated in your original request.

To provide legal certainty to the owner of the personal data and to us as the Responsible Party, in case the Owner makes his/her ARCO Rights request via e-mail, this must be from a personal e-mail account that has been previously registered in our databases, in this case the one granted in his/her role as a client of Grupo Jumex.

For more information about this Privacy Notice or any questions about how to exercise your Rights of Access, Rectification, Cancellation and Opposition (ARCO), limit the use or revoke your consent, you should send an email to:  
privacidad@jumex.com.mx , with the subject “Information on ARCO Rights” or call the telephone number: (55) 5699-1999 on the days and hours previously mentioned.

CONSENT
-------

We do not collect or process sensitive personal data of our **End Customers**, so it is not necessary to express your consent to the processing of these expressly in this document.

Unless you exercise any of your Rights of Access, Rectification, Cancellation or Opposition (ARCO), limit the use or revoke consent to the processing of your personal data, we consider that you accept the provisions of this Integral Privacy Notice.

PROCEDURE TO REVOKE CONSENT GRANTED FOR THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------

In case you want to revoke your consent to the processing of your personal data, you must perform the same procedure established in the section “Rights of Access, Rectification, Cancellation and Opposition (ARCO)”.

Your request will be subject to review by our Data Controller. If a legal exception is not fulfilled or that there is no legal provision that subjects us to process your personal data, your request will be granted, and you will be notified of the decision within 10 business days.

FOR THE EXCLUSIVE USE OF GRUPO JUMEX
------------------------------------

LIMITATION ON USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL DATA
-------------------------------------------------

In the case of our **End Clients**, at any time you have the option to limit the use and/or disclosure of personal data by submitting it in writing at the address indicated above and addressed to the Data Controller indicating in your request the scope of limitation to the use or disclosure that you want to set, accompanied by a copy of your official identification at the time of submitting your writing.

Your request will be subject to review by our Data Controller. If it does not comply with a legal exception or there is no legal provision that subjects us to processing your personal data, your request will be granted, and you will be notified of the decision within 10 working days.

FOR COMMERCIAL ISSUES
---------------------

Visit The Consumer Protection Federal Bureau website where the Public Consumer Registry (RPC) provided for in the Federal Consumer Protection Law is at your disposal, where you will decide on the use of your personal data in the commercial, tourism and telecommunications sectors.

COMPETENT AUTHORITY
-------------------

After having exercised your Rights of Access, Rectification, Cancellation or Opposition: having limited the use or disclosure of your personal data, or having revoked your consent of your personal data, if you consider that we have made any omission or any action in violation of the provisions of the Federal Law on Protection of Personal Data Held by Private Parties, we hereby notify you that the competent Mexican authority before which you must file your complaint or disagreement is the National Institute of Transparency, Access to Information and Protection of Personal Data (INAI).

USE OF COOKIES, WEB BEACONS OR OTHER SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
---------------------------------------------------------

On our website [www.grupojumex.mx](http://www.grupojumex.mx/) and its domains, we collect personal data through cookies and web beacons. This  
information allows us to learn:

* Ads you visit on our site (anonymously)
* IP address from which you visit us (anonymously)
* In general, your location and your activity in our website, to optimize the search for your preferred services within our official website.
* Date and time of your visit (anonymously)
* Browser information: program and version (anonymously)
* Information you exchange with our site (anonymously)
* Visited pages (anonymously form)

To opt-out of us collecting this data about your visit, we recommend that you consult your browser’s privacy settings. Following the information for the most commonly used browsers:

* _Chrome_ (support.google.com/chrome/answer/114836?hl=es-419);
* Firefox (support.mozilla.org/es/kb/configuracion-de-la-privacidad-el-historial-de-nav);
* Internet Explorer (windows.microsoft.com/es-es/windows/change-internet-explorer-privacy-settings#1TC=windows-7;
* Safari (support.apple.com/kb/HT1677?viewlocale=es\_ES)

UPDATES
-------

This Integral Privacy Notice will be updated in the future due to modifications to the legal framework regarding personal data protection, changes in Grupo Jumex’s business model, new personal data collected and/or changes in its purposes.

Updates and modifications made to this Integral Privacy Notice will be communicated via the email account provided in the customer service process, it will also be available on our official website www.grupojumex.mx in the “Privacy Notice” section and in the ‘Information’ section of our official profiles on social networks.

**Date of last update: December 01, 2020.**

### Contact us

### Explore

### Get in touch

® 2020 Jumex. All rights reserved.
